Guide to the Stages Theater records, 1978-2017 MS 740
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Stages Theater records
1978-2017
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Stages Theater (Houston, Tex.)
MS 740
51 Linear Feet 48 boxes
Stages Theater records contain materials related to play production programs and other production materials from 1978-2016, press clippings, annual gala and events records, administrative records, photographs, and circa 200 audio and video recordings in analog formats such as VHS and audio cassette.
Biographical / Historical
Founded in 1978, Stages has grown to become Houston's leading mid-sized theatre company, the city's sixth largest nonprofit performing arts producer overall, and the largest outside of Houston's downtown theatre district. Stages is one of the region's leading artistic employers, producing an average of 12 productions per year totaling more than 380 performances and welcoming 65,000+ visitors each season.
Content Description
Stages Theater records contain materials related to play production programs and other production materials from 1978-2016, press clippings, annual gala and events records, administrative records, photographs, and circa 200 audio and video recordings in analog formats such as VHS and audio cassette.
Conditions Governing Access
This material is open for research, except for the Development series, which includes restricted personal financial data regarding donations and requires written permission from Stages Theater for access, until 2038.
Stored offsite at the Library Service Center and require 24-hour notice for retrieval. Please contact the Woodson Research Center at 713-348-2586 or woodson@rice.edu for more information.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
These records were donated by Stages Theater in 2018.
Index Terms
Subjects
Arts -- Texas; Theater; Performing arts
Document Types
photographs; programs (documents); clippings (information artifacts); playbills; videotapes; minutes (administrative records); notes; letters (correspondence); typescripts
Subjects (Corporations)
Stages Theater (Houston, Tex.)
- Series I. Seasons (boxes 1-12), 1978-2016
  - 1978-1979
    - Newsclippings (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Photographs and Bios (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Photographs and Bios (early seasons) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Press Releases (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Programs and Art (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - 1979-1980
    - Newsclippings (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Photographs and Bios (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Press Releases (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Programs and Art (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - 1980-1981
    - Newsclippings (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Photographs and Bios (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Press Releases (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Programs and Art (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - 1981-1982
    - Newsclippings (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 14-15)
    - Photographs and Bios (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Programs and Art (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - 1982-1983
    - Administration and Contact Sheets (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Newsclippings (2 folders) (Box 1, Folder 19-20)
    - Photographs and Bios (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Press Releases (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Programs and Art (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Special Projects (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - 1983-1984
    - Photographs and Bios (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Press Releases (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Programs and Art (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Special Events (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - 1984-1985
    - Advertisements (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Newsclippings (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Photographs and Bios (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Press Releases (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Programs and Art (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Special Events (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 1985-1986
    - Administrative and contact sheets (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Newsclippings (3 folders) (Box 2, Folder 14-16)
    - Photographs and Bios (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Press Releases (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Programs and Art (Box 2, Folder 19-20)
    - Special Events (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - 1987-1988
    - Administrative (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Advertisements (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Early Stages (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Newsclippings (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 2-3)
    - Photographs and Bios (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Programs and Art (2 folders) (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
    - Press Releases (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Scripts (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Special Events (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1988-1989
    - Advertisements (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Newsclippings (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Photographs and Bios (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Press Releases (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Programs and Art (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Special Events (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 1989-1990
    - Administrative and Contact Sheets (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Advertisements (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Early Stages (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Newsclippings (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Photographs and Bios (2 folders) (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
    - Press Releases (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Scripts (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Special Events (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 1990-1991
    - Administrative (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Advertisements (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Newsclippings (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Photographs and Bios (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Press Releases (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Programs and Art (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Scripts (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Special Events (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 1991-1992
    - Administrative and Contact Sheets (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Advertisements (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Early Stages Study Guides (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Newsclippings (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Photographs and Bios (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Press Releases (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Programs and Art (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Scripts (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Special Events (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Texas Playwright Festival (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - 1992-1993
    - Administrative (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Advertisements (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Early Stages Study Guides (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Newsclippings (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Photographs and Bios (2 folders) (Box 5, Folder 11-12)
    - Press Releases (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Programs and Art (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Scripts and Music (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Wine Fest (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - 1993-1994
    - Administrative (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Advertisements (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Early Stages Study Guides (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Newsclippings (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Photographs and Bios (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Press Releases (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Programs and Art (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Scripts (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Wine Fest (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - 1994-1995
    - Administrative and contacts (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Advertisements (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Early Stages Study Guides (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Newsclippings (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Photos and Bios (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Press releases (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Programs and art (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Scripts (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - 1995-1996
    - Advertisements (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Administrative (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Early Stages Study Guides (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Clippings (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Photographs and Bios (Box 7, Folder 7.7)
    - Press releases (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Programs and art (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Scripts (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Texas Playwrights Festival (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - 1996-1997
    - Administrative and contacts (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Early Stages advertisements (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Early Stages programs (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Early Stages study guides (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Newsclippings (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Photographs and bios (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Press releases (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Programs and art (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Scripts (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Special Events (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - 1997-1998
    - Advertisements (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Early Stages Study Guides (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - General and subscriptions (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Newsclippings (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Photographs and bios (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Press releases (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Programs and art (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Scripts (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Special events (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - 1998-1999
    - Administrative and contact sheets (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Advertisements (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Awards (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Newsclippings (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Photographs and bios (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Programs and art (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Press releases (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Special events (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Subscriptions (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - House Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - 1999-2000
    - Administrative and contacts (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Advertisements (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Newsclippings (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Photographs and bios (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Press releases (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Programs (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Special events (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - 2000-2001
    - Administrative and contacts (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Advertisements (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Newsclippings (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Photographs and bios (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Press releases (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Production notes (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Programs (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Special events (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Subscriptions and general (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 2001-2002
    - Photographs and bios (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Toys Performance Reports, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Romance, Romance Performance Reports, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Little Witch Performance Report, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - The Pavilion Performances Reports, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Heart of a Woman Performance Reports, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Cinderella Performance Reports, 2001 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - The Laramie Project Performance Reports, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Firebird Production Reports, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Production notes (1 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Production notes (2 of 2) (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Rehearsal Schedule, 2001-2002 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Programs (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Programs (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 2002-2003
    - Production Notes (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Production Notes (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Programs (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 2003-2004
    - Newsclippings (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Programs (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - 2004-2005
    - Newsclippings (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Press Releases (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Production Notes (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Programs (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Scripts (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - 2005-2006
    - General (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Press Releases (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Programs (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Honky Tonk Angels (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Program and Production Notes: Silence (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Program and Production Notes: Baby - a Musical (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - The Toys take over Christmas (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Program and Production Notes: Searching for Eden (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Program and Production Notes: An Infinite Ache (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Dead Guy (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Program and Production Notes: Nickel and Dimed (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 2006-2007
    - Season Programs (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Great American Trailer Park Musical (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Cook (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Program and Production Notes: Five Course Love (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Program and Production Notes: Amy's View (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Program and Production Notes: An American Brat (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Program and Production Notes: Indian Cowboy (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Program and Production Notes: I Am My Own Wife (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Program and Production Notes: Zero Hour (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - 2007-2008
    - Season programs (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Program and Production Notes: Late Nite Catechism (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Program and Production Notes: Souvenir (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Program and Production Notes: Black Pearl Sings (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Program and Production Notes: Sister's Christmas Catechism - The Mystery of the Magi's Gold (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Program and Production Notes: Altar Boyz (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Program and Production Notes: Late Nite Catechism 2 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Unseen (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Program and Production Notes: Lady (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Program and Production Notes: Rounding Third (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - 2008-2009
    - Season programs (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Program and Production Notes: Mr. Marmalade (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Program and Production Notes: Always...Patsy Cline (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Program and Production Notes: Unbeatable (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Program and Production Notes: Panto - Cinderella (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Program and Production Notes: Taking Flight (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Program and Production Notes: Rabbit Hole (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Program and Production Notes: Wallflower (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Program and Production Notes: Grey Gardens (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - 2009-2010
    - Season programs (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Andrews Brothers (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Program and Production Notes: Southern Rapture (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Program and Production Notes: Panto - Sleeping Beauty (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Program and Production Notes: A Picasso (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Program and Production Notes: Speech and Debate (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Program and Production Notes: Late Night Catechism 3 - Til Death Do Us Part (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Program and Production Notes: Man from Nebraska (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - 2010-2011
    - Season programs (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Complete History of America (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Marvelous Wonderettes (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Program and Production Notes: Auntie Mame (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Program and Production Notes: Panto - Pinocchio (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Program and Production Notes: Oh, the Humanity (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Program and Production Notes: Yankee Tavern (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Program and Production Notes: Late Night Catechism 4 - Sister's Easter Catechism (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Program and Production Notes: Four Places (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Program and Production Notes: Odd and the Frost Giants (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - 2011-2012
    - Season programs (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Great American Trailer Park Musical (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Program and Production Notes: Hank Williams - Lost Highway (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Blonde, The Brunette, and the Vengeful Redhead (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Program and Production Notes: Winter Wonderettes (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Program and Production Notes: Panto - Red Riding Hood (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Program and Production Notes: Mistakes were Made (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Program and Production Notes: Late Night Catechism (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Program and Production Notes: In the Next Room (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Program and Production Notes: A Stubborn Woman (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Unexpected Man (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Program and Production Notes: Next to Normal (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - 2012-2013
    - Season programs (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Program and Production Notes: Life could be a Dream (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Program and Production Notes: Steel Magnolias (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Program and Production Notes: 2 Pianos, 4 Hands (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Winter Wonderettes (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Program and Production Notes: Panto - Mother Goose (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Program and Production Notes: Wittenberg (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Program and Production Notes: the Language Archive (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Program and Production Notes: Always...Patsy Cline (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Program and Production Notes: Dollhouse (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - 2013-2014
    - Season programs (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Marvelous Wonderettes - Caps and Gowns (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Program and Production Notes: Late Night Catechism - Las Vegas (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Program and Production Notes: Veronica's Room (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Great American Trailer Park Christmas Musical (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Program and Production Notes: Panto - Goldilocks (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Program and Production Notes: Failure - A Love Story (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Program and Production Notes: Sexy Laundry (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Program and Production Notes: Gidion's Knot (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Whipping Man (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Program and Production Notes: Xanadu (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Program and Production Notes: Pete 'n Keely (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Program and Production Notes: Full Gallop (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Program and Production Notes: Marie Antoinette (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Program and Production Notes: Sister Christmas Catechism - The Mystery of the Magi's Gold (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Program and Production Notes: Panto - Rapunzel (and Zombies) (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Program and Production Notes: Character Man (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Program and Production Notes: Girls Night the Musical (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Program and Production Notes: Stupid F-ing Bird (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Program and Production Notes: Bad Jews (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Spiritualist (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - 2015-2016
    - Season programs (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Honky Tonk Angels (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Program and Production Notes: Driving Miss Daisy (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Elaborate Entrance of Chad Deity (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Program and Production Notes: Sister's Christmas Catechism - The Mystery of the Magi's Gold (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Program and Production Notes: Panto - Snow Queen - Unfrozen (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Program and Production Notes: The Book of Maggie (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Program and Production Notes: Straight White Men (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Program and Production Notes: End of the Rainbow (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Program and Production Notes: Miss Teen (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Program and Production Notes: I and You (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Program and Production Notes: Big Fish (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Undated Programs (Box 12, Folder 58)
- Series II: Administration and Board records (boxes 13-25), 1978-2017
  - Theater Showcase into Stages, 1978-1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Stages Repertoire, 1978-2002 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Stages Theater History and Facts, Repertoires, 1978-2012 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Grant Applications & Correspondence with Cultural Arts Council of Houston, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence with Cultural Arts Council of Houston, 1980 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Budgets, grants, fundraising, federal taxes, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - First Texas Playwright Festival, 1981-1982 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Fundraising contacts/records (1/2), 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Fundraising contacts/records (2/2), 1982-1983 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Business Resources, 1985-1996 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Marketing Plan, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Corporate Donations, 1986-1993 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Staff Handbook, 1986-1993 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - The Black Book, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Board Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Board of Directors Lists and Meetings, 1988-1990 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Board Nominating Committee, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Marketing Analysis, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Underwriting Requests: A, 1989-2001 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Underwriting Requests: B, 1989-2001 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Board of Directors vitae & Correspondence, 1990s (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Board Minutes, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Advisory Board Operation, 1990-1993 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Budget reports, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Sponsorship Opportunities, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Impresarios, charter members, 1990 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Impresarios, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Mission Statement, 1991-1999 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors Lists, 1991-1994 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Board Minutes, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Budget reports, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Audit Statements, 1991-1994 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Contact List, 1991-1992 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Individual contributions, 1991-1994 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Employee Performance Appraisal Program, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Fundraising study for Stages as compared to other arts organizations, 1991-02 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - StageHands, 1991 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - By-Laws, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Board of Directors List, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Board Minutes, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Executive Board Minutes Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Report to the Mayor & City Council, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Building Committee, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Building Memos, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Financial Statements, 1992-1993 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Impresarios, Lists, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Security, 1992-1994 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Historical Designation, 1992-1995 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Development Committee, 1992-2001 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Architectural Studies (Cisneros & Partners), 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - News coverage correspondence regarding stages at Star Engraving Building, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Ticket Price & Attendance, 1992-1993 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - By-laws as amended, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors Meetings, 1993-08-17 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1993-11-16 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Projected revenues, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Impresarios, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Stages Impresarios Lists & Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Corporate Stars fundraising campaign, 1993-1994 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Renovation planning for Star Engraving Building, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Star Engraving/Allen Philbrick, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Milwaukee Repertory Theater Marketing Survey, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Corporation Filing Fee, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - USO Donations, 1993-1995 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - National Labor Relations Board, 1993-1996 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Board of Directors, 1994-1995 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Board of Directors correspondence & reports, 1994-1996 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Board Meeting Minutes (1/2), 1994-2000 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Board Meeting Minutes (2/2), 1994-2000 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Budget Planning, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Civic Association Directory, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Texas Commission on the Arts, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - AFTRA, 1994-1997 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Ticketmaster, 1994-1996 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Foundation Board Proposals, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Board of Directors lists, 1995-1997 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, 1995-02-28 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Board Planning Meeting, 1995-10 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Board nominating committee, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Executive Committee, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Budget reports, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Budget Reports, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Corporate Stars fundraising campaign, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Impresarios, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Proposed Budget - Stages School, 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 13)